So I want to talk right now to people who don't care about Israel.
So if you are somebody who does not care about Israel and their alignment with politicians,
I'd love to bring you up and have you on right now.
So you can go right here and I request to come on camera.
And I would love to talk to you.
So again, if you are somebody that doesn't care about Jasmine Crockett's alignment with Israel,
I would love to have you on and bring you up.
And I just want to have a conversation.
Because I have some thoughts and I would love to have a conversation.
So again, here is my, like you can ask.
I mean, here's a request where you can request to come on.
Um, and, um, we don't have anybody requesting to come on.
So I'm gonna, I'm gonna give it a little bit of a second, but I would, I've genuinely,
well, it's interesting when I say genuinely and people are like, what do you mean?
Um, you said, why not have it with her?
Jasmine Crockett is not going to have a public conversation with me.
Also, this is not, this is not specifically about Jasmine.
So I want to have a conversation with those who do not care about, um, so I did bring someone up.
Hello.
Why do you all request?
Like you have to make an effort to request.
It's not something that the app does by itself.
So I have no idea why you guys go to the effort to make a request.
And then when I bring you up, you, you deny.
Oh, you say you didn't mean to.
Okay.
Okay, Corey.
Corey was at work, by the way.
That looked like a FedEx trip.
Corey.
Corey, Corey looked like he was at work.
He said, whoa, don't try and get me fired now.
Okay.
This is Rainbow Jamer.
Whoa.
Did you do this on accident?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
No problem.
I'm at work, though.
I don't want to get you in trouble.
So I will see you another time, Rainbow Jamer.
Thank you.
Y'all, and I love that y'all are not doing these people work.
Okay.
I love that y'all are at work not doing these people work.
Because I low-key took the day off for myself today.
Okay.
I low-key took the day off for myself.
I said, Amanda, you need a day to just rest your brain because it's been a long month.
So I am asking y'all, if you are somebody that does not feel that Israel has anything to do with Texas politics or that it should be a factor in Jasmine Crockett or James Tallarico's candidacy,
please hit this little box right here.
Hit this little box right here.
Corey, you...
Corey!
So nobody...
So nobody wants to have this conversation?
Why does nobody want to have this conversation?
Okay.
Here's another person.
Not too cool in state property.
Get down or lay down.
Y'all are scared?
Okay.
Nobody's here.
Why won't y'all...
Why won't y'all come on?
So here's what I think.
I think that a lot of you all actually have not seen any of what's going on in Palestine.
That's actually what I think.
I think a lot of you all have actually not seen what's going on in Palestine.
Because...
Don't get me wrong.
There's a whole other very legitimate argument for the ways in which Texas is so deeply embroiled in Israeli theft that it is even more so than other states.
It is incredibly...
It is 1,000% ruining your lives in Texas, their relationship to Israel.
That is a fact.
However, I was lying here.
And it dawned on me that those of y'all who are saying Israel doesn't matter, Palestine doesn't matter, you haven't seen.
Because, you know, the algorithm doesn't show everybody the same thing.
Did you know that?
The algorithm doesn't show everybody the same thing.
So everybody is not going to see footage about things that they don't have interest in.
And so when I see people saying, oh, Palestine is not our business, I have decided that the only people that could actually say that are people who have not seen what's happening in Palestine.
Because there's no version of seeing that and being like, oh, it doesn't matter.
It's just not.
Like, there just isn't.
Like, it dawned on me because I know black people.
You know what I mean?
Like, I really do.
I know black people and I know the South.
And the only way that the black people, because I'm from the South.
Like, I grew up in Orlando, Florida.
And so it was like, it hit me just now.
Like, oh, no, they don't, they don't, Diana.
They don't.
You must remember.
I think it's very important that you must remember that we are under a psychological operation.
All the time.
Okay?
We are constantly barraged with propaganda in this nation.
And on these apps, which is where most people get their information, we are completely subjected to a controlled algorithm that prevents there being,
even my page is shadow banned.
I do have a cash app.
It's just a seals.
Thank you.
You can also send badges on here.
But, you know, we, like, my page is shadow banned, right?
So there's a, there's a, I was told, oh, I got chocolate on my hand.
I'm greedy.
I was told by Instagram, your page will no longer be shown to new followers.
The only people who will see your page are people who already follow you.
So I am not able to get across to anybody who does not know my work.
So here's a person here, diddied something.
Now, they have been going off in the chat saying that if I really wanted to talk to Jasmine Crockett, I would tag her.
I have Jasmine Crockett's phone number.
I texted Jasmine Crockett and she has not responded to my text, so I stopped texting her.
You know, you all seem to think that we're on the same page, that we're in the same level.
We're not on the same level.
I've been in this longer than you.
I've been working longer than you.
I know more people than you.
I know more information than you.
You and I are not the same.
I talk about what I know about.
I am shadow banned.
Why are you arguing that I'm not shadow banned?
So when you all say weird shit like that to me, it's bizarre.
It's bizarre.
Also, because I am not the one running for Senate.
I am not the one running for the U.S. Senate.
The people.
Get you all acting like I need to be chasing after Jasmine Crockett or Cory Booker.
I don't need to go after none of those people.
They should be coming after us.
And that's the dynamic.
Y'all keep messing up.
That is where you all keep getting it twisted.
We are not in a scenario where we have to capitulate to politicians and we keep doing this.
Why do we not understand this?
And by the way, every black leader that we iconocize, that we idolize,
have been against all of these systems that you all seem to be so mesmerized by.
And so that being how I was raised, and I know how so many of you all were raised,
and so I'm like, there is no way that all of these people who went to church,
who help old ladies, there's no way that y'all could have been seeing what's going on in Palestine
and act as if that is irrelevant.
In addition to the reality that Texas continues to spend taxpayer dollars
to buy Israeli bonds that fund the Israeli government
and provide programs and assistance to Israelis that do not get provided to you.
This is a hallmark position that should be taken.
And when people see Zoran Mamdani and say, wow, he did something different,
nobody should be running on anything less than what he was running on.
So for people to be saying to me, I am not making sense
by acknowledging Israel's role in Texas politics is nonsensical.
For people to think that there is going to be some sort of shift.
If you just want a black woman in position just to say she's a black woman in position, say that.
But don't say we want a black woman in position who's going to help us
when you are not actually supporting a black woman who's going to come in position to do something different than anyone else.
That's not practical.
Someone here asked, but why are you targeting Texas when Jasmine is running?
I want you to say that out loud to yourself.
Why am I targeting Texas when Jasmine is running?
I need to also acknowledge that the United States Senate holds positions that are in their seat for six years.
Senate positions are longer holds and are more senior to United States representatives' positions.
It is a majority rule.
And as a member of the United States, anybody running for any role in Congress is my business.
And for the record, anybody running anywhere is my business.
I am a citizen in the United States.
Texas, like Ange Kahn said here, is the eighth largest economy, not just in the United States, in the world.
Arritive!
That there has to be a geopolitical consciousness.
Okay, let me block this person because some of y'all are just actual pricks and I don't have the time.
It's a geopolitical consciousness that has to be had by anyone in Congress.
How can you be voting on war, on money being sent to other countries, on defense?
How can you be voting on any of these things if you don't have a geopolitical consciousness of how the United States is involved in these things and how it affects individuals in the United States?
How can you be voting on any of these things if you don't have a geopolitical consciousness?
No, Jen Uli, I don't think they know what's going on in Palestine.
I don't.
I don't think these people have seen what's going on in Palestine.
And I'm going to say that because what's been going on in Palestine has been going on for quite some time.
And it wasn't until 2021 that it even made its way to my consciousness.
It's been going on for a hundred years.
So here we have Paul Fousey Amor.
What should we do?
Now, I probably, I think you're probably a bot because people ask that and I am, at this point, you're a bot.
However, what I continue to make aware to you is that you can make demands of candidates.
The United is funding the war in Sudan.
Yet you all are buying Dubai chocolate all over the place.
There's no chocolate in Dubai.
There's no cocoa in Dubai.
Well, Paul, if you're aware of that, then I'm not sure why you're asking me what you should do.
Israel spends as their number one export.
There are no diamonds in Israel.
They are constantly saying, Amanda, you're not talking about the United States and Sudan.
You're not talking about the United States and Congo.
You're not talking about Israel, et cetera.
I'm always talking about them.
I saw a Benjamin Netanyahu stand up and say that there would be no United States if it wasn't for Jewish people.
Anything changes is because behavior changes.
I'm going to say this again because I really, really, really, really care.
However, the only way anything changes is because behavior changes.
That's it.
It seems simple.
However, it's not as simple as you may think because some people don't know where to start with the behavior.
Start with yourself.
Operated in the past.
When it comes to your awareness of politics, has it been more related to your own individual issues?
Has it been related to just your own, like, city?
Has it been related directly to race?
Has it been related to solely the United States?
When you are actually wanting better for yourself, you're going to have to change behaviors.
I appreciate you all in here letting people know about views from Amanda Land.
I would love for you all to subscribe to my YouTube page, AmandaSealsTV.
And we've done a lot of work there.
It's going to be coming on a year.
I think we're at a year since the show started.
And we've been spending that time learning and growing and becoming more informed.
I'm seeing people who are staunchly for Jasmine Crockett.
But when asked, what do you plan to do to support her, they don't have an answer.
They don't have an answer.
If I say, what are your plans to support this candidate and you don't have an answer, you're not really interested in supporting that candidate.
You're actually more interested in feeling right, I guess, about whatever you believe in.
I believe that James Tallarico is a more viable candidate to win.
I also believe that on a values level, James Tallarico has presented himself as someone willing to go to bat against the most racist of racists in Texas.
And I will say that as a white Christian man, that is a very important asset.
I saw someone say today that they heard him speak out against Israel.
I have not seen that.
He has taken money from Zionist Miriam Adelson, who also supported Donald Trump.
So I do not support that whatsoever.
And I do believe that at this juncture, all candidates that are going to get any level of, that are going to provide any level of real genuine change have to be willing to be loudly and enthusiastically different.
And they have to be willing to put their heads on the chopping block.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
They have to be willing to go up against the machine.
If they are not willing to go up against the machine, you can bet your life that they are selling somebody out to feed the machine.
And it may not be you this time, but it may be some of you.
It may be you next time.
And so when I am trying to encourage you, it is because I love you.
And no, that is not what Jasmine is doing.
Because the machine is more than just Donald Trump.
The machine is also Democrats.
And if you're not going up against the Democrats, and you're not going up against Israelis, and you're not going up against Zionists, you're not going up against that which is keeping the machine going.
You've got Bill Clinton and Hillary Clinton running around talking about how valuable Israel is.
That should let you know.
That should be an indicator to you that something is afoot.
Any time opposing sides are funded by the same bottom line, they are absolutely being ruled by the actual force that you should be challenging.
Now, I have seen this.
Someone said that she's going up against the Supreme Court justices.
I'm not sure what that means.
So I would love for someone to educate me because I have not seen that.
I'm not sure what that actually is in reference to.
In what way is Jasmine Crockett going up against the Supreme Court?
So if anyone has more information on that, I would love for you to just educate me on what that's about.
Because I haven't – I haven't – I saw that twice today, and I didn't further research it yet.
But I would love to hear what that's all about.
So if anybody has that information, you can either type it in the chat, or you can come up on the live and educate us on what that's actually in reference to.
And illuminate us.
Thank you, 900, baby.
John Cornyn, what words do you want for John Cornyn?
This is the other part that's always odd to me.
Why am I going up against the person who's already up against me?
That's not the person that I'm trying to battle.
Because I already know what they're about.
So the person that I'm trying to address is the person who actually wants my votes.
Okay, this person says, the Senate has oversight of the Supreme Court.
She's going for the snake's head.
The Supreme Court has been doing some foul stuff.
Okay, I'm going to hold your hand as I say this.
We got to wake up from the fantasy.
We got to wake up from the fantasy, y'all.
These people are a part of generational systems of oppression.
They are engaging in practices of mind control and practices of theft that go over all of our heads.
Jasmine Crockett does not have the individual power to dismantle them.
That is not shade to Jasmine Crockett.
That is reality.
I do not have the individual power to dismantle them.
None of us do.
They have been building their power with threads of evil and wickedness for generations.
And any time we engage by pulling one of those threads, we become entangled in their web.
Do you understand?
They are a web of blackmail, a web of deceit, a web of colonialism.
And what they do as parasites is they are consistently sending out tethers to constrict folks.
The only way to kill them, to kill their power, is to prevent them from being able to use you as a host.
So we have to be a force of unity.
Now here is somebody named Trey DeBaby.
If none of us got the power, then this conversation is pointless.
And you are essentially wasting your breath.
You know, Harriet Tubman was married.
Harriet Tubman was married to a friend, I mean to a free man named John Tubman.
He was a free black man.
He was a free black man named Trey DeBaby.
Do you know why they ended up getting divorced?
Because he would not go north with her when she decided to escape.
He would not go north with her because he did not believe that it was a smart thing to do for her to escape.
Essentially, he felt that the devil you know is better than the devil you don't.
So since she had a master who wasn't that bad, he felt it safer for her to stay.
Imagine.
Imagine if she had listened.
Imagine if she had let his fear, his lack of wonder, his privileged position as a free man present her from getting her own freedom.
Imagine.
No.
Too many of us want to be John Tubman.
Too many of us want to stick to the evil and the devil we know.
Not realizing that we don't actually know that devil.
We don't.
And so many of you who are constantly saying Israel doesn't matter.
You don't even know anything about Israel.
You don't know anything about Palestine.
You have not witnessed.
You have not connected.
You have not interacted.
Because if you had, it would be undeniable for you that there is a connection.
In the same way that that undeniability is what connected the minister, Louis Farrakhan, is what connected Malcolm X, is what connected June Jordan, is what connected Alice Walker, is what connected Angela Davis, is what connected the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, is what connected John Lewis and Stokely Carmichael.
And I can go on and on and on, there is no way, there is no way that if you had actually interacted, that you would be able to sit idly by and say, I don't care.
No, no, no, I don't believe that.
So what you do is you hide yourself.
You prevent yourself from having to know.
And I invite you to expand yourself.
And I would say, even just on the basis of, it is Palestinians, it is the Palestinian struggle, it is the Palestinian connection to their land, to their faith, and to their people, that woke me out of the indoctrination of this nation that has no regard for its land.
That commodifies its land that commodifies its faith and that compromises its people.
You should consider yourself fortunate that it is someone else's suffering that can wake you up and not your own.
Did you hear what I said?
You should consider yourself fortunate that it is someone else's suffering that can awaken you and not your own.
And you need to acknowledge that it is your labor being used to cause their suffering.
And it is your labor being used to undermine your own advancement.
I just saw someone say one of the dumbest statements I've seen in a long time.
They said it is very odd to them when they see intelligent people with cats.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Should I have a bearded dragon?
Thank you.
I'm tired too.
This cat's name is Sankara.
Palmasina Sankara, named for the late Thomas Sankara of Burkina Faso, who was taken out by an individual who was supplanted by the CIA to be a puppet.
Now, after years of being a puppet and capitulating to France, there was a coup.
And he was replaced.
And the people of Burkina Faso said, we're only going to allow you to remain if you do what we want.
And we want our country back.
We don't want colonialism.
And that man did not do as the people bidded.
And thus, there was another coup, a people's revolution.
And that is what put Ibram Traore in position in Burkina Faso, the people.
There was a political education movement that took place that allowed people to understand their power,
that allowed people to free themselves from the limitations that colonialism had placed them in.
Exactly.
All good.
Hello, Babas.
I love you.
And that is what we must do.
We must educate ourselves.
And anybody who indicts in 2025 is saying, I don't need to care about something that they see their entire United States government caring about doesn't actually care.
There is absolutely no way you can consciously say, I don't care about Israel, when you see the United States sending billions and billions and billions of dollars.
You don't care.
You can't possibly care.
Because you're willing to ignore something that is so blatantly served.
So I implore you, saying Israel doesn't matter.
One, you are being prevented from living your best life with the work that you do because of Israel.
And two, on a moral, human level, until you care about other humans, hear me when I say this, until you care, the evil will continue.
And I mean that and I believe that with every fiber of my body and soul, that as long as we find ourselves following the imperial mindset of, I don't need to care about what's happening to people who aren't me, we are only pushing their mindset forward.
And we are strengthening the power of the storm that we will be caught in.
And I don't think y'all even understand how powerful the storm is.
And what is happening right now is that these people who wanted to be all powerful, they have created a storm that even they can't control.
They think they're in control.
They're not.
They're out of control.
And the earth is showing them that.
Hi, Lumumba.
I wish you all a good night.
I hope that you have listened.
I hope that this conversation brought you forward.
And I hope you will reconsider your position on how you as a member of this nation need to engage in your future.
May the force be with you.
And tomorrow morning, you can join us on YouTube at 10 a.m.
Eastern for views from Amanda Land.
Go on over and subscribe at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
And we'll see you next time.
We'll see you next time.